Email: seerapuharshanandini@gmail.com

Phone: +91 6300224352

Profile:

https://harshanandini.github.io/profile/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/harshanandini/ GitHub: https://github.com/HarshaNandini

Technical Skills and Tools:

Core Languages

Java, JavaScript, C, Python

Web Development

HTML, CSS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Express

JS, XML, BootStrap

Query Languages

SQL, PL/SQL

Version Control

Git

Certifications:

- 1. Data Analytics Foundations Google.
- 2. Introduction to Programming using Python Microsoft.
- 3. Azure AI Fundamentals Microsoft.
- 4. Elements of AI University of Helsinki.
- 5. Oracle Certified Foundations Assocaite – Oracle.
- 6. Analytical and Soft Skills –Dr.Lankapalli Bullayya College of Engg.

Education:

B.Tech Computer Science

Engineering, Dr.Lankapalli Bullayya College of Engineering, Andhra University, 2020-2024, 8.34CGPA

Intermediate MPC, Sri Chaitanya Junior College, 2018-2020, 9.01 GPA

10th CBSE, Sri Krishna Vidya Mandir, 2017-2018, 83%

Interests:

Painting, Dancing

Harsha Nandini Seerapu

Software Development Engineer

Career Summary:

Having 3+ months experience in software development using Java, JavaScript and SQL, I am focusing more on learning new technologies. I am good in web development tools such as Node JS, React JS, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, XML and version control system using Git. I am good in analytical skills, communication skills and inter-personal skills.

Experience and Internship:

- 1. **Software Development Trainee** at **Yalamanchili Software Exports**, Visakhapatnam Since 15 Apr 2024 till date
- 2. **Web Developer Intern** at **Technohacks EduTech**, Mumbai 1 month from 10 Aug 2023 to 09 Sep 2023

Key Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, ReactJS

Projects:

- 1. Plagiarism Checker A Python Language Modeling project for final year CSE deployed with streamlit (source, demo)
- 2. Battleship Game A dynamic JavaScript game (<u>source</u>, <u>demo</u>)
- 3. <u>Animated clock</u> An animated analog clock with CSS styling
- 4. <u>Ball Game</u> A JavaScript game with Keyboard arrow control events
- 5. <u>Dynamic Page</u> Online Shopping portal home page
- 6. <u>Drawing Pad</u> A JavaScript drawing board with mouse control events

Workshops:

- Introduction to Web Development and Open Source
 Workshop 2 days Microsoft
- Web Designing and Figma tools 2 days Google
- Canva Designing Tools Workshop 2 days Google